Guide to the William Rainey Harper Papers 1872-1938
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Correspondence, May 8 - 29, 1899, Abbott, Prof. F.F. Clason, George B. Committee of the Dearborn Alumnae Association Crandall, Rev. L.A. Culter, Helen Freund Fritsche, Herman Hancock, Harris (missing) Harper, Samuel (son) Hicks, Frederick C. Hirsch, Dr. Hudson, R. Hyde, Dr. James Nevins McPherson, Dr. S.J. Mensterberg, Prof. Moxom, Rev. P.S. Murdock, Thomas Wallace, Edwin S. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, May 31 - June 15, 1899, Angell, Prof. Brown, Prof. Charles R. Cooke, Majorie Coulter Crane, Cornelia Hale, George E. Hale, W.G. Henderson, Hon. David B. Ingalls, Dr. Linn, Mrs. W.R. McKee McLeish, Andrew Munsterberg, Hugo Rabb, Robert Morris Selden, Dr. Joseph H. Vincent, Bishop John H. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, June 16 - 29, 1899, Bartlett, A.C. Caldwell, E.D. Chamberlin, Georgia Congdon, Mrs. Dickerson, J.S. Gage, Hon. Lyman J. Hall, G. Stanley Johnson, Rossiter Lawrence, Rev. Wm. M. Morris, Mrs. C.D. Northrup, Pres. Cyrus Soares, T.G. Vincent, George E. Wilson, Alfred M. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, June 20 - July 22, 1899, Abbott, F.F. Butler, Nathaniel Buttrick, Wallace Chamberlain, Georgia Cleveland, Hon. Grover Day, Wilson, M. Faunce, W.H.P. Gallup, Frank A. Harper, Samuel (Father) Hendrickson, Prof. Hobbs, Mr. Howell, Charles Leacock, Stephen Mead, Prof. Pearson, Principal Reynolds, Miss Rowlands, H. O. Vincent, George (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, July 24 - August 8, 1899, Beales, W.R. Blaine, Mrs. Clark, Soloman H. Davidson, Herbert M. Goodspeed, George S. Harper, Samuel (Father) Haskell, Mrs. Hemke, Albert P. James, Prof. Johnson, Rossiter Maddocks, Caroline S. McKee, W.P. Patrick, F.W. Pentuff, John R. Tufts, Mr. Will, Thomas E. Yerkes, Charles T. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, August 8 - 21, 1899, Angell, Prof. Ayer, Ed., A.C. Bartlett, Chauncy J.Blair, C.L. Hutchinson, H.F. McCormick, O.S.A. Sprague, Geo. C. Walker, and William B. Walker Beales, W. R. Cobb, Henry Ives Dods, Rev. Marcus Harper, Mr. Ingalls, Dr. King, Henry Churchill Lovett, R.M. Potter, O.W. Slocum, Pres. Spalding, Bishop Stetson, Pres. Talbot, Miss Turner, E.A. Vincent, Prof. Wallace, Elizabeth (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, August 21 - September 7, 1899, Angell Arnett Barton, Enos M. Breasted Cameron, Miss M. Edith Claghorn, Kate H. Cobb, Mr. Culver, Miss Donaldson, H. H. Fairbairn, Principal A.M. Harper, Paul (son) James, Mr. Johnson, Rossiter Liddell, Mrs. Ida Miller, Miss Emma Raymond, Pres. Jerome H. Selz, Harry Smith, George Adam Von Holst, Prof. Tighe, Rev. D.J. Truax, Charles (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, September 7 - 13, 1899, Blackstone, Mr. Butler, N. Caldwell, E.L. Chase, W.J. Clark, Blanche Davis, Mr. Bradley M. Dunham, F.A. Hale, George E. Harper, Pres. E.T. Hyde, Dr. James N. James Kirkland, Pres. J.H. Mandel, Mr. Leon Selz, Harry Sisson, E.O. Small, Dr. Smith, George Adam Von Holst Whitman, Prof. E.O. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, September 14 -20, 1899, Adams, Pres. C.K. Barnes, Prof. Belfield, H.H. Boyd, J.H. Braithwaite, Rev. E.E. Burton, E.D. Butler, Nicholas Murray Coulter Crandall, L.A. Dewey, Melvil Enfield, Charles Hadley, Pres. Arthur T. Haynes, A.J. Hines, F.H. Holden W.H. Howerth, Mr. Jackson, J.L. Lawrence, W.M. Loba, J.F. Lowden, H.O. MacKenzie, W.D. Mallory, H.F. Mathews, Shailer McAfee, W.M. Parker, A.K. Perry, Rev. Robinson, Geo. L. Seymour, T.D. Smith, Henry Justin Turner, Prof. F.J. Von Holst, Prof. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, September 22 - 30, 1899, Atkins, Mrs. E.C. Baldwin Comstock, Prof. Geo. C. Davenport, Dr. Charles B. Durham, F.A. Harper, Samuel (father) Henderson Jesse, Prof. Moody, Dwight L. Moulton, F.R. Stevens, Prof. R. H. Terry, B.S. Von Holst, Prof. Young, Ella Flagg (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, October 3—November 13, 1899, Bosworth, Prof. E.J. Boyd, James Harrington Curry, Hon. J.L.M. Curtiss, Charles C. Goodspeed Gurney, Mr. Hall, Jabez Higgins, Ned Ames Kendrick, J.L. Low, Pres. Seth Low. MacClintock, Mr. Mitchell, John J. Reed, J.J. Robertson, George E. Rockefeller, John D. Schwill, F. Sisson, Mr. Talbot, Miss Terry, Mr. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, November 14 - December 18, 1899, Adams, Mrs. Geo. Bryce, Hon. James Caton, Arthur J. Corson, B.F. Dewey, Melvil Field, Marshall Harper, James Harrison, Mayor Carter Ingalls, Dr. E. Fletcher Johnson, Franklin Kelly, Mrs. Elizaeth G. Kent, Sydney Linn, Mrs. Nellie B. McCormick, Harold Miller, Charles Pond, James B. Smith, J. Archy Van Invegen, Clarence P. Von Holst, H.V. Walker, Geo. C. Zueblin, Prof. Charles (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, December 18 - 30, 1899, Anderson, S.B. Barton, Enos M. Bowen, L.W. Demmon, Stephen D. Field, W.T. Fleming, Blanche Fulton, Chancellor R.B. Gates, P.W. Harper, Samuel (father) Jesse Judson, H. P. Knott, Henry A. Mandel, Leon Manly, Prof. McWilliams, Lafayette Palmer, Mrs. Potter Rockefeller Rosenberg, Jacob Ryerson Seitz, Morris Walker, Mrs. William W. Wilson, Prof. Woodrow (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, January 1 - 25, 1900, Aked, Mr. and Mrs. C.F. Alumnae of Dearborn Seminary Angell, Pres. Ballantine, W.G. Bartlett, A.C. Bell, Graham Butler, Nicholas Murray Churchman, Editor Corey, Francis Dixson, Mrs. Dougherty, N.C. Forbes, Pres. J.F. Gurley, Mr. Randall, S.B. Salisbury Shumway, Edgar S. Smith, J. Archy Stableton, Supt. J.K. Vincent, Mr. Von Holleben, Dr. Von Holst, Prof. Wilkinson, Prof. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, January 26 - February 12, 1900, Adams, Mrs. George E. Ames, Prof. E.S. Bishop, Judge C.A. Bulkley, Miss Coulter Crane, R.T. Dickson, Prof. L.E. Fisher, Fannie G. Foster, Mrs. Nancy Friedman, Chas. A. Hadley, Pres. (Yale) Hancock, Mr. Harper, Samuel (father) Hughitt, Pres. Manly Morehouse, Dr. H.L. Porter, James F. Reynolds, Miss Ryerson Stetson, Pres. Talbot, Miss Tufts, Dr. James (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, February 12 - 24, 1900, Barker, Dr. L.F. Bennett, Prof. A.A. Bowerman, George F. Buck, C.D. Carpenter, F. I. Chicago Historical Society Forbes, Pres. J.F. Hand, R.C. Harris, Rendel Hulbert, Dean Johnson, Franklin Jones, Miss Laura Leitner, Almena Paul, Rev. David Robertson, Prof. A.T. Smith, J.A. Votaw, C.W. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, February 24 - 28, 1900, Barnes, Prof. Harper, J.H. Irving, Sir Henry James, Prof. E.J; Lal, Vaneshi Lowden, F.M. Nickerson, Mrs. Samuel Nolan, J.J. Ryerson Salisbury Smyth, Dr. Newman Votaw (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, March 1 - 20, 1900, Alderman, Pres. E.A. Bartlett, A.C. Blackstone, Mrs. Butts, Annice B. Cobb, Mary Rena Driver, Prof. S.R. Harrison, Caskie Keen, William C. Kelly, Mrs. Kent, Sydney Lyman, Dr. Henry Macleish, Andrew Mahaffey, Prof. J.P. Mandel, Leon Michelson Moloney, W.A. Rose, A.C. Ryerson Sprague, O.S.A. The World Van Schaak, Peter Walker, George C. Wilson, P.H. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, March 20 - April 6, 1900, Adams, Charles F. Andrews, N.L. Angell Bartlett, A.C. Breasted Broadus, Edmund K. The Dial Fallows, Bishop Samuel Forbes, Mr. Hollingsworth, Supt. T.E. Morrissey, Rev. A. Newberry Library Nickerson, Pres. Palmer, Mrs. Potter Rubens, Harry Schleppenbach, Albert Shirk, Milton Sprague, O.S.A. Strickland, E.F. Ting-fang, Wu Wishart, Alfred (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, April 6 - April 24, 1900, Abbott Acting President of Purdue University Buck, C.D. Eillis, Mrs. Sumner Fang, Wu Ting Harris, Rendell Kelly, Mrs. Lloyd, Henry Long, J.H. McClurg, A.C. Secretaries of American Group, International Association for the Advancement of Science, Arts and Education Shepardson Sponner, Edwin V. Turner, Prof. Van Siclen, George W. unidentified (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, of Acting President May 2 - June 21, 1900, Clark, S.H. Fleet, A. F. Sellon, L.T. Townsend, R. D. unidentified (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, June 22 - June 30, 1900, Barnes, Clifford W. Bass, Rev. L.D. Burton Dames, Pres. Colonial Foster, Miss Garton, Rev. R. Hadley, Pres. (Yale) Harper, Samuel (son) Ingals, Dr. Kohlsaat, Judge C.C. The Times (London) Nickerson, Mrs. Nordell, Rev. P.A. Peck, F.W. Peckham, Prof. G.A. Pentuff, Dean J.R. Sellon, L.J. Shearer, S.J. Stecker, Dr. Henry Taylor, Pres. Van Siclen, Geo. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - July 3 - August 20, 1900, Burnham, D.H. Carmen, Geo. N. Collector of Customs Colored Student's Club Faunce, W. H. P. Fay, C.N. Kohlsaat, Judge C.C. Loeb, Prof. Lovett Moulton, Prof. Otis, E.A. Parker, Dr. Francis L. Rhees, Rush Shaw, Albert Slocum, Pres. Smith, F.A. Smith, Geo. Adam Stagg, A. A. Wessels, F.J. Wright, R.R. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, August 24 - 31, 1900, Arnold, Dr. Ferreira, John E. Harmon, Miss Hart, Mr. McCormick, Pres. Rhees, Pres. Rush Shorey (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, September 1 - 26, 1900, Allen, J.M. Colestock, Henry T. Ferreira Harper, R.F. Harris, James Hayes, Mrs. R.C. Hays, Hon. John (Secretary of State) Kelly, Mrs. Lloyd, Nellie M. Mouton, F.R. Schaeffer, N.C. Sellon, Miss Grace Shepard, Irwin (Sec. NEA) The Time Herald (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, September 27 - October 22, 1900, Atwood, W.W. Carr, Rev. Norman Corrington, W. Greenwood, C.J. Harper, R.F. Harvey, L.D. Haupt, Paul Lloyd, Nellie McCormick, Pres. S.B. Salisbury, R.D. Sanders, Prof. Frank K. Simpson, Mrs. D.W. Williamson, Mr. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, October 22 - November 12, 1900, Bridgman, H.A. Carr, N. Corrington, W. Driver, Prof. S.R. Gale, Henry Haupt, Paul Hyde, Dr. James Nevins Knox, Reuben Lovett McCormick, S.B. Peele, C.D.M Schroeder, P.C. Senn, Dr. Nicholas Small Williamson, J.E. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, November 14 - December 11, 1900, Brown, A.L. (Johns Hopkins) Carr, N. Chainey, George Curtis, John B. Dixson, Zella Allen Ellison, Anna E. Enfield, Mrs. Gordon, C.U. (Chicago Post Master) Hazard, Caroline Hubbard, H.D. McLane, T.L.. (Johns Hopkins) Noyes, L.W. Post, Judson Sanders, Prof. F.K. Stout, Howard M. Taylor, Charles H. Vincent, Mr. Williams, Wardner (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, December 12 - 13, 1900, Bridgman, H.A. Brown, A.L. (Johns Hopkins) Campbell, Mary Cook, Agnes, Spofford Crane, C.R. Enfield, Mrs. Charles Houghteling of Yale Bi-centennial Fund Committee Jacobs, Miss Louise Johnson, Rev. T.C. McLane, T.L. (Johns Hopkins) Mitchell, Rev. J.B. Rew, Henry C. Sharp, Rev. Geo. W. Yale Club (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, January 4 - 30, 1900, Burton, E.D. Enfield, Mrs. Charles Faunce, W.H.P. Goodman, Edward Hadley, Arthur T. Hale, H.G. Hamilton, D.G. Howe, Florence Leach, Abby Marsh, R.L. McCarthy, M.H. McLaughlin, A.C. Mitchell, J.B. Moncrief, Prof. J.W. Myers, Mr. Osler, Dr. William Ranson, Caroline L. Raycroft, J.E. Schoolcraft, H.L. Small, Albion Westcott, O. S. Williams, Warder (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, January 30 - February 16, 1901, Andrus, Ethylle Blake, E. Nelson Cavanaugh, John Crane, Charles R. Flint, Mrs. Hale, W.G. Hansel, J.W. for the Secretarial Institute and Training School of YMCA Leonard, Rev. George E. Low, Pres. Seth McLeish, Bruce Munger, T.T. Parker, Col. Francis W. Ridgway, E.J. Rosenberg, Bernhard Salisbury Senn, Dr. N. Williams, Wardner Wolf, L. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, February 18 - March 7, 1901, Appleton, W. W. Cavanaugh, Rev. John D. Appleton and Co. Dickerson, J.S. Dudley, Gertrude Harrison, Frederic Hulley, Lincoln Johnson, R.U. Johnston, J. Jordan, E.O. Laing Laughlin, J. Laurence McClure, S. S. Munger, Dr. T.T. Ridgway, E.J. Rondeau, W.H. Soughtgate, R.H. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, March 7 - March 30, 1901, Alderman, Edwin A. Dymond, Edith L. Evans, H.A. Goodspeed, Geo. Greene, Samuel H. Hale, George E. Hitchcock, Annie Heath, D.C. Heckman, Wallace Hulley, Lincoln Jordan, E.O. McKinley, Pres. Nickerson, U.P. Northrup, G.W. Robinson, Miss Rowden, H.H. Salisbury Senn, Dr. Sharp, Geo. W. Swisher, Lucy E. Wescott, O.S. (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, April 1 - 30, 1901, Raymond, Jerome H. Brown, W.H. Blair, F. G. Colwell, R.S. Conaty, T.J. Day, Edward Elmer, Franklin D. Gardner, Geo. A. Gilbert, M. D. Hatch, Henry D. Hulley, Lincoln Josephson, Aksel G.S. Lawrence, Wm. M. Maxwell McClure, T.C. McKee, Mrs. H.P. McLeish Moore, Ernest C. Moore, J. Colin Reynolds, Myra Rowe, Stuart Swisher, Lucy E. Van Liew, Charles (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, May 3 - June 3, 1901, Alderman, Pres. Burton, E. D. Colwell Day, Rev. Edward Flint, Mrs. Funk, I.K. Hadley, Pres. Hancher, John W. Harrison, Mayor Carter H. James Luckey, J.S. Parker, Supt. A.O. Ricketts, C.L. Small Stuart, Prof. Lewis (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, June 5 - 29, 1901, Darnell, Laura W. Freeman, Justice Henry V. Hancher, Pres. Hulley, Lincoln Locke, George H. (School Review) Pearsons, D.K. Raycroft, Dr. J.E. Raymond, C. Rexford Search, Preston W. Small Spelman, Lucy N. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, July 1 - August 2, 1901, Bartlett, A.C. Beecher, Willis J. Brinkerhoff, Lieut.-Col. H.R. Doherty, Eleanor Donaldson Fargo, W.F. Hubbard, Harry Johnson, Franklin Locke Mac Veagh, Franklin MacMillan Co. Moehle, C.E. (American Lithographic Company) Parker, A.O. Pobedonostreff, Mr. C. Sebastian, John (Chi. RI and Pacific RR) Smith, G.B. Tulane, President of (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, August 3 - 28, 1901, Almstedt, Hermann Angell, Prof. Barker, Dr. Lewellys F. Davis Dixon, Mr. Donaldson Elliott, Rev. W.A. Fleet, Col. (Culver) Gilbert, Will H. Hyde, James Llewellyn, Frank J. MacLean, Mr. Swift, George F. Votaw, C.W. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, August 29 - September 29, 1901, Brown, Prof. C.R. Crane, R.T. Crissey, Forrest (Saturday Evening Post) Dickerson, J.S. Dixson, Mrs. Eaton, T.T. Fleet, Col. Hadley, William A. Harper and Brothers Hyde, James H. Llewellyn, F.L. Rabb, Mrs. R.M. Shepardson, F.W. Tennant, J.H. (The Worlds) Wood, Nathan E. Ynasa, Kichiro Zueblin (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, October 3 - 28, 1901, Adams, C.K. Brown, Dr. Alfred C. Brown, Scott Comptroller Coons, C.D. Doubleday, Page and Co. Elliott, W.A. Frost Hadley, Pres. Harper, R.F. Herricks Marsden, W.H.P. Parker, Dr. Powell, Dr. T.W. Ricketts, C.L. Sears, T.H. (Harper and Brothers) Triningham, Anne E. Wilson, Walter H. Woolley, Pres. Mary E. (Mt. Holyoke) unidentified (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, October 29 - December 3, 1901, Alderman, Pres. Barker, Dr. Llewellys Curtis, Edward L. Elliott, W.A. Evans, Louis (Sec. Apollo Club) Fruchte, Amelia Goodspeed, George Greene, Dr. Samuel Harper, R.F. Heckman, Wallace James, Mr. Keeley (Chicago Tribune) Mainwaring, J.T. Park, Mary W. Parker, Mr. Powell, T.W. Triningham, Anne E. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, December 3 - 31, 1901, Campbell, Miss Crissey, Forrest Curtis, Edward Goodspeed, Geo. Greene, Samuel H. Hall, Chas. Cuthbert Harris, N.W. Hulbert, Dean E.B. Johnson, Balfour Jordan, Elsie Fay Myers, Mr. Park, Mrs. Mary W. Parker, A.K. Pine, J.B. Ramey, Ray R. Rust, Henry A. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, January 2 - 17, 1902, Abbott, Frank Frost Anderson of Anti-Saloon league Anderson, William Barnes, C.R. Burton Chandler, Henry P. Crissey, Forrest Goodspeed, George Harris, Pres. Graham Heath, D.C. Kalamatiano, S. Laughlin, J.L. Parker, F.W. Revell, Alexander H. Revell, Fleming H. Schutze, Martin Sears, J.H. Wellauer, Jacob (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, January 16 - February 4, 1902, Abbott, F.F. Barnes, C.R. Corbin, H.C. Driver, Prof. S.R. Freeman, F.D. Harper, R.F. James, Edmund J. Kern, W.C. (missing) Knowles, Mary H. McClintock, W.D. Myers, Mr. Sears, J. H. Smith, Mr. State Normal School, Resident Regent Stratton, S.W. Sweet, Robert B. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, February 6 - March 4, 1902, Barnes, C.R. Burton Corbin, Adjutant Gen. Donnelley, T.E. Engler, E.A. Greene, Samuel H. Hall, Charles Cuthbert Harper, J.H. Harper, R.F. Harris, W.T. Lord, Hon. George P. McGinnett, W.S. Moore, Willis L. Myers, Mr. Rabb, Robert Morris Smith, Willard A. Stratton, S.W. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, March 4 to April 12, 1902, Anderson, W.H. Feddersen, Emilie Franklin, W.B. Gates, Dr. Owen H. Harlan, Pres. Jackman, Mr. Jordan, Herbert R. Lester, A.G. Lord, Geo. P. Mathews, Robert E. Moore, Henry W. Myers, Mr. Parker, Dr. Prince, Dr. B.D. Rolfe, Mrs. Mabel Parker Shaw, Albert Shepard, Mrs. Shepardson Vincent (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, April 14 - May 16, 1902, D. Appleton and Co. Dowie, Dr. James Alexander Draper, Pres. A.S. Fellows, George Emory Fenn, W.W. Ferreira, J. Emerson Harper, R.F. (Brother) Keeley, James Matthews Pine, John B. Terry, Mr. Votaw Wilson, Aflred M. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, May 18 - June 18, 1902, Alumni Andrews, E. Benjamin Angell, Pres. James B. Billings, Dr. Doherty, N.C. Gale Higinbotham, H.N. Jones, J.B.E. Jones, Lester B. Martyn, E.W. McLeish, Mrs. Andrew Miles, Col. (Supt. West Point) Morgan, O.T. Oliver, Charles Sisson, E.O. Swain, Pres. Thurber, Charles H. Vincent, Geo. E. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, June 19 - 30 1902, Foreman, Henry G. Foster, Volney W. Harper, R.F. (brother) Hyde, Dr. Oliver, Charles C. Rosenthal, Julius Sisson Smith, Mrs. Justin A. Swain, Pres. Wright, N.S. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, July 2 - August 20, 1902, Allen, J.P. Cortelyou, Geo. B. Foreman, Henry J. Foster, G.B. Hall, G. Stanley Hanna, Mark Harlan, Pres. Jesse, R.H. Jordan, mr Milspaugh, Pres. J.F. Rodriguez, Damaso Soldan, Louis Tatlock, John Weinstock, H. Woodruff, H.C. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, August 22 - September 29, 1902, Association for the Protection of the Adironacks Cleary, Kate M. Davis, M.J. Dickerson, J.S. Englander, Rabbi Henry Goodspeed, Geo. Hall, E.B. Hall, Locke, and Co. Hegstrom, W.H. James, D. Willis Jones, Lester B. Jordan Kato, A. Magwood, Robert H. Peabody, Susan Wade Torrey, C.C. Weinstock, H. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, September 29 - October 23, 1902, Alderman, Pres. Chamberlin, T.C. Cooper, Mary Crown Prince of Siam Ford, Prof. James W. Gale Hall of Hall, Locke, and Co. Heckman, W. James, Pres. Jordan Kato, A. Myers (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, October 24 - December 9, 1902, Addams, Jane American Correspondence, School for Nurses Bartlett, A.C. Crane, C.R. Dewey, John Dougherty, N.C. Dudley, Miss Fuller, Roy E. Hall of Hall, Locke and Co, Harvey, Geo of Harper and Bros. Hyde, James H. Kelly, Mrs. Elizabeth G. Low, Hon. Seth Myers Rainey, Mrs. William Rice, Alfred B. Savage, M.J. Votaw Weaver, C.H. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, December 9 - 20, 1902, Curtis, John B. Francis, David R. Halsey, E.A. Henderson, Emma M. Hyde, James H. Jesse, Pres. Myers, R. Parker, F.W. Rust, H.A. Sisson, E.O. Thompson, James Westfall (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, January 3 - 29, 1903, Barnes, Pres. Clifford W. Foreman, Henry G. Gillespie, H.L. Goodspeed, Geo. Hall, E.B. Harris, W.T. Hoyt, Wayland Mills, Supt. Myers, Mr. Noble, Samuel Rabb, Rev. Robt. M. Reel, Supt. Estelle Revell, Alexander Reynolds, Lewis G. Rust, H. A. Sisson Strong, Josiah (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, February 3 - 26, 1903, American Associaltion for the Advancement of Science Fiske, Horace Spencer Foreman, H.G. Hall and Locke Co. Hall, Pres. E.B. Hayden, F.L. Hyde, Pres. William D. Jordan, W.G. Maclean, Mr. H.H. McNair, Mr. Mufee, H.O. Parker, Francis W. Reel, Estelle Robertson, George E. Rust Sisson Swanson, C.O. Williams, E.F. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, February 27 - April 2, 1903, Beck, Carl Carter, Thos. H. Cross, Dr. George Fiske, H.S. Hale, W.G. Hall and Locke Co. Hurd, Mrs. Dwight H. Hyde, J.H. Matthew, W.H. Murfee Parker, Francis W. Rabb, R.M. Rainey, Mrs. Elanor B. Stewart, Mrs. Mary B. Webster, R.W. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, April 2 - 20, 1903, Beck, Carl Briggs, Prof. C.A. Brown, Charles Rufus Capps Davenport, Chas. B. Hastings, James Jackson, Rev. J.L. Lathrop, Bryan Lester, A.G. Meadows, Geo. B. Nelson, A.H. Otis, Philo A. Raycroft Reynolds, Miss Simpson, G.B. Smith, Alexander Smythe, Rev. D.N. Stewart, Mrs. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, April 20-30, 1903, Briggs, C.A. Bull, A. A. Hastings Johnson, J.B. Maclean Rogers, Dr. L.D. Smith, Alexander (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, May 1 - July 2, 1903, Briggs, C. A. Crane, C.R. Hale, W.G. Hall, O.L. Harper, Samuel (father) Heckman Johnson, J.B. Leichner, L. (Richard Wagner Monument in Berlin) Matz, Evelyn Meadows, G.B. Miller, Newman Mother Mary Emily Nash, C.E. Ramsay, F.P. Smith, Alex Smith, Mrs. George Adam West, Victor J. Wight, Geo. Of Hannah and Hogg, Family Purveyors (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, September 2 - October 19, 1903, Adee, A.A. Alderman, E.A. Barnes, Rev. L.C. Curtiss, Samuel Ives Dewey Dougherty, N.C. Hamilton, Wm. A. Hart, Chas. F. Lawrence, Jos. S. MacLean Miller, Newman Myers, Mr. Parker, Dr. Ramsay, F.P. Smith, Geo. Adam Trustees (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, October 20 - November 28, 1903, Alderman, Pres. Amer. Book Co. Brown, Henry T. Chamberlain, Miss Crandall, L.A. Dewey, J. Hale, Mrs. W.G. Hamilton, W.A. Higinbotham, H.N. Johnson, J.A. Lawrence, Wm. H. Randall, Rev. J. Herman Silva, Frank P. Stone, Pres., of Pudue Webster, R. W. White, Mrs. Lovell (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, December 1 - 31, 1903, Armstrong, T.H. Bradlety Polytechnic Institute, Trustees Brown, Charles Rufus Capps, Edward Cherry, Mary Dewey, J. Dewey, Mrs. Dougherty, N.C. Hammond, H.A. Hulbert, Dr. Judson, Edward Judson, H. P. Jules, J. Jusserand Launderville, J.H. Loeb, William Meechem, Floyd R. Sanders, M.J. Shepardson (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, January 2 - 30, 1904, Bonet-Maury, G. Dewey Donaldson, H. H. Fay, Lois R. Foreman, Henry G. Gale, Henry Hale, W. C. Harper's Weekly, Editor Hatfield, Mrs. Hyde, Pres. D.W. Kunz, Geo. A. Raycroft, J.E. Shepardson Sisson, Edward O. Van Hise, Pres. Zueblin, Charles (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, January 30 - February 12, 1904, Capps, Dr. J.A. Curtis, S. Elliott Dewey Fay, Lois Garrison, L.A. Goodspeed, Geo. S. Harper, Harry H. Henderson, Prof. Archibald Johnson, Luke G. Lovett Lowden, Frank O. MacLean Michelson Murphy, Starr J.' Senn, Dr. Nicholas Sisson, E.O. Strauchon, E. Marguerite Votaw (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, February 12 - 29, 1904, Bartlett, A.C. Bunzel, Mrs. Coons, clarence d. Curtis, Elliott Downing, Augustus S. Gale Goodspeed, George S. Hale, W. G. Hana, Mrs. Mark Harper, Samuel (Son) Johnson, Luke G. Levering, Frank H. McKee, W.P. Rowlands, Rev. H.O. Salisbury Strauchon, Marguerite Warren, Mr. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, February 29 - March 26, 1904, Braislin, Rev. Edward Burton, E.D. Buttrick, Wallace Crane, C..R Dudley, Gertrude East High School, four students Hegstrom, Rev. V.H. Hulshart, John Levering, Rev. Frank H. Lovett, Mr. Lyte, E.O. McKee, W.P. McLeish, Mrs. Rockefeller, John D. Roers, James Gamle Shortall, John G. Sisson, E.O. Small Symmes, Frances Newton Willison, Henrietta and Lulu McCoy (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, March 26 - April 18, 1904, Annable, Rev. E.W. Braislin, Rev. E. Buttrick, W. Committee of First Baptist Church Dewey Dickerson, J.S. Dudley, Miss East High School, four students Elliott, A.J. Hegstrom, V.H. Jesse, Pres. R.H. Jordan, Herbert R. Levering, Rev. F.H. Lillie, Frank R. Lyte, E.O. McClure, Thomas D. McCullough, T.G. Mead, G. H. Public of Hyde Park Rogers, James Gamble Symmes, Miss Frances Von Holst, Mrs. Willison, Miss and Miss McCoy (Box 7, Folder 9)